

NADYA PAK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER 1 YEAR EXPERIENCE

Summary:

Hello.

I am Nadya, 31 years old, Front-End Developer with creative and logical thinking. Love coding and create something new. Open-minded to new technologies like **VueJs**, **React**, easy-going and responsible. I would like to join a friendly team with interesting tasks and to do my best to contribute to purpose-led company's goals.

Experience:

2019-2021 ALROSA PJSC (Moscow) Frontend-developer

ALROSA is the leader of the world diamond mining industry. There I was responsible for developing UI of web application based on **Angular 8**.

2010-2019 ALROSA PISC (Moscow) Sales support specialist

Education:

2018-2019

Courses Web-developer "Skillbox" (Moscow), student.

2015-2018

Higher School of Economics, Bachelor's degree, IT business analytics.

2007-2013

Moscow State Mining University (MSMU), Process engineer.

Skills:

- JavaScript
- Typescript
- Angular
- 00P
- HTML
- CSS
- REST
- MySQL
- Git
- Agile and Scrum
- Trello
- Iira
- Azure

Languages:

- English
- Hebrew
- Russian

Tools:

- Windows & Linux
- Visual Studio Code
- SublimeText

Contacts:

Location: Bat -Yam, Israel

E-mail: Nadegda.park1707@gmail.com

Phone: (+972) 58-553-69-21

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/park-nadegda

Portfolio: https://pakdim.com/pak